I carry high my craven flag,
my ally I'm gonna fly and let my
struggles shoot me through the sky!
It'd be a pity if we
lingered here and let our
pretty sparks of life
blend aloud and disappear?
There may be fog that even you can't
navigate If someone strong like you is lost,
then who will set me straight?
Cause when the waves cast my heart adrift.
It's been your kindness and your strength.
That would free me from the mist.
And just like that.
We move on.
Sail to a new dawn.
Weigh anchor right as high as you can.
I assure I don't need anger.
I go fast as I am, yeah.
I hear you laughing like
you're numb to it all.
While we're dashing together.
No, we're never gonna fall, you know.
The whole world may now be my enemy.
Water's slow, but I ain't backing down.
So long as I'm free, yeah.
Thought I'd give it, come
round the current with me.
All in, wake up bright and early.
Making for the peak we go.
Having fun?
Yeah, this is the best
day ever! Hey, you guys!
I found some shaved ice right over there!
Let's go!
Papaya, fly!
I've never had shaved ice
before, that sounds so neat!
We gotta go, Nami! Come on!
Hurry, hurry!
What if it melts?
They've got a ton of flavors!
Oh, how do I pick?
Wait, I know!
I want red bean soup flavor!
How fast things!
There's no end to this.
I know you told me to go,
but I can't leave you.
You must!
Momonosuke, I don't understand.
Why won't you let me help you fight?
This matter is ours to settle, Yamato.
Step back!
Stop wasting my time!
Just bring me Straw Hat, little baby!
Uh-huh!
Curts of a ring!
I'll end this! Sneak pole!
Scrolling Chouchou!
FIRE!
EXCEPT!
Burn to ashes!
You baby scum!
Just kidding.
FIRE BREAK FORWARD!
I'm an Admiral of the Navy,
you arrogant little dope!
You think I could rise to that position
with such an obvious weakness?!
Water gives life to humans and the
rest of the natural world as well.
I'll show you.
What are you doing?!
Rhyzo!
We need a new plan!
His branches keep growing back!
Hold on, I'm coming!
Think, Cat, he must have some weakness!
Maybe if we cut all of his
branches at once somehow!
Rwahahahaha!
Wominosuke...
Why?
Rwahahahaha!
Hidden stairs?
Oh!
Seems we've been sniffed out.
You were with the rest of the crew,
so naturally I got suspicious.
Don't act like I'm some kind of hyena.
Do watch your step.
It's a bit moldy down here.
I tried to hide this route from
Orochi and Kaido, to no avail.
As you know, their lead
performer, Jack, is a fishman.
So despite my best efforts, they
found the polyglyph in no time.
What does being a fishman
have to do with it?
You'll see soon enough.
This is a lot of stares.
How far down are you going to take us?
How far a few hundred
years or so I suppose.
Mr Tang where was that light coming from?
There's a glass window that lets you look
outside you can take a
quick peek if you like.
We're already at the bottom of the sea.
That's cheating.
Can you see out there?
A whole city underwater?
That's the land of Wano from
about 800 years in the past.
The original, you might say.
Eight hundred years ago.
What happened back then?
A fine question.
I understand the how and the
when, but the why is lost to time.
The reason it's so well preserved is
because that's not actually seawater.
This is what I do know.
The land of Wano was once located at a
base of a huge mountain called Fujiyama.
At one point, walls were created,
enclosing the island, causing
rainfall to accumulate.
As time passed,
the town became Unbelievable,
so the people moved up the
mountain and built a new country,
far above what you're seeing now.
And that's the modern-day land of Juana?
Exactly.
Here's our destination.
A road poneglyph.
This is the third one that
we've found on our journey.
Just one more.
And we can make our way to Laugh Tale.
We're in a small cave at the foot of
Fujiyama, where the water doesn't reach.
This isn't the only
thing buried down here.
It is said the ancient weapon
Pluton lies further beneath us.
I've never seen the weapon myself and
I'm afraid I can't show it to you now.
In order to retrieve
it the giant walls must
first be removed opening
the borders of Wano.
Not only lowers our defenses but unleashes
the power of an ancient
weapon on the world.
How frightful that is
quite the risk but that was
Odin's wish why would he
want that for this country.
Well I've told you everything that was
passed down to me I haven't a clue what.
Odin learned to cross the sea, so
his intentions remain a mystery.
Strupee!
Hey, Beppo!
The shaved ice here is great!
What? Where? I need it!
I need it now!
Leave our country alone!
Lord Babonosuke!
You're only human.
You're no match for Mother Nature.
By the way,
in case you haven't caught on yet, the
reason I'm here is because Kaido is gone.
He was a deterrent.
Even if he ran this country into the
ground, But he kept your enemies at bay.
But lucky for you, we're not
planning to invade right now.
So if you want me to go away,
then bring me Straw Hat Luffy!
Momonosuke!
Call the Straw Hats now!
It'll be fine, they won't lose to him!
I cannot do that!
Huh?
It's the same reason why
I cannot ask you for aid.
You've spent your entire life
imprisoned on Onigashima.
But now, you can finally be free.
So I will send you off properly.
I've been depending on Luffy and his
friends to see me through these trials.
But we who remain in this country
must be able to stand on our own.
We cannot rely on those who are departing.
This is our country to protect.
We must drive out its
enemies with our own power!
Momonosuke.
Get out of here, you monster!
Why?
Why must you fail me now?
Gotta say, you're a pretty
pathetic excuse for a dragon.
I've had just about enough
of your stupid games.
Leave this country!
It finally worked!
That's the power of our lord!
He already wields that
attack like Kaido himself!
I said go!
No!
The water will never come back!
Dammit!
You little brats!
Drop them out!
He's doing it!
He has the full power of a dragon now!
Perhaps, but his aim still
leaves much to be desired.
Damn, kid.
What the hell?
You trying to burn down the whole city?
You want to fight?
Fine by me.
You really think I'm scared
of some kind of wannabe?
Try that again and I'll
skewer you from head to tail!
Why can't I move?
Conqueror's Haki...
Who the hell is there?
No it can't be the red hair
pirates why are they here
Come on boss you can't just
bust your Haki out without
warning the new recruits can't
handle it Yet I'm not saying
you have to be nice mr marine
but these pirates fought hard
to change history Don't you
think you'd be in a poor sport,
stomping out flowers before
you know what color they bloom?
Does this new era frighten you so much?
Is that why?
Listen, I'm not trying to fight you guys.
At least not yet.
Yeah, all right, I get it.
It worked!
You did it, Momonosuke!
I think he's leaving!
You've defended the land of
Wano, just like you said!
I can protect this country.
I can protect my home.
Of course!
You're incredible!
He ran away.
You did pretty good, Momo.
Look at that.
They don't need us.
I assume the rest of you felt
that overwhelming Haki here.
Yeah, that sure was crazy, wasn't it?
Made me think of an old friend for a sec
Are you all right?
Shinobu Raizo
They just need fluids and some rest
they'll be better soon I promise.
That is a relief he was
right I hate to agree
with him but the whole world feared Kaido.
As long as he held Wano in his iron grip
no one would dare set foot on his shores.
Forgive me to my great
shame I was in cutie at
the time and wholly
ignorant of your struggle.
It all worked out fine
nobody blames you Karoo.
Lord Momonosuke really put in the work.
He saved us all.
By the way, how is Otsuru?
It's been quite a while.
She's hurt, but she will live.
She was burned when Okobore Town set fire.
I failed to protect her too.
There you are, Otsuru.
I heard King came back to see you. He did.
He had to hurry back to
the Flower Capital though.
You're from the capital, too, dear.
Go be with your love. I will.
And soon.
I've waited long enough already.
You know, even after 20 years, she's as
beautiful as she was on our wedding day.
All right.
Enough mushy stuff.
You're becoming even
more of a dog than me.
It's all right.
I think it's sweet.
Rizal, you're awake.
Is there something you want?
Come closer.
What is it, friend?
I want a wife.
Hounding after the ladies even now.
Go to sleep.
This is bananas!
Carrot!
Hey, what's about it?
Duke Dogstorm and Master
Catviper have some big news.
They need you to come right now.
Ah, finally showed up,
huh? Hey, guys. What's up?
You got some news for me?
Why is everybody here?
You gotta keep us waiting.
Carrot, we would like you, Kara,
to rule the Mokumo dukedom.
I get to roll!
Hooray!
Works for me!
I can't do that!
Don't make me!
I would be awful, I swear!
The thing is, the Catanine
decided to stay in Wano.
We're still samurai of the Kozuki clan.
So it is our duty to keep
Lord Momonosuke safe.
You, Karoo, have traveled with Luffy,
so you, Karoo, have a broader
view of the world than other Minx.
That's what the next
generation will need the most.
We believe in you, Karoo.
Oh, like me, though!
There's tons of Minx stronger than I am!
Should you ask them first?
No, they should not!
It is the duty of the strong
to protect our country!
I support their decision.
And I will support you, Tia, too.
Carrot, Yotia can do this.
Pedro's will lives in your heart.
Pedro's will?
We're counting on you, Carrot.
Tomorrow belongs to the young,
and so should Zoe, I say.
You really are grandfather?
Indeed.
Kozuki Odin was my son.
I'm so glad you're alive and well.
I'm sorry.
I've been so ashamed that
I almost didn't tell you.
I couldn't save Odin after all.
What's worse, I couldn't save the
land of Wano despite being Shogun.
I failed you. Forgive me.
I have always wanted to meet you.
Me as well?
You're too kind.
I'm still shocked.
You look just like Odin did
at your age, Momonosuke.
I'm shocked as well.
But more than anything,
I'm happy to have a family.
You cannot know what that means
to us after our parents' loss.
So please don't apologize.
No matter what happened, we're so
glad to have you with us today.
My heart leapt into my throat
to think that he was among us.
I never dared to dream such a thing.
Lord Tsukiyaki is alive and well.
His disguise was truly flawless.
I knew you'd figured out my
secret, but what was I to say?
You did wear a Tang mask.
I'm afraid that draws attention.
We certainly didn't think that
you were an average swordsmith.
We feigned ignorance out of
respect, but we weren't fooled.
Isn't that right, Master Keen?
Yes, of course!
My apologies.
I put you through so much.
I can tell you about the
land of Wano's history.
I stayed alive all these
years so I could do so.
But that's all I'm good for anymore.
So I beg you, let me cede the throne
and let the nation think I'm dead.
This is a new era.
It is yours to create.
Knowing that you are alive is enough.
That gives us strength.
You're telling me Pluton
is buried down there?
Yes.
I didn't get to see it
in person, mind you.
But it is here.
I honestly wasn't even sure if it existed.
Is that the big ship Franky burned
the blueprints for correct an
ancient weapon with the name of
a god they said would you want to
have it Luffy the weapon no thanks
i'm good that's no surprise but
after Odin traveled the seas he
wanted to unleash it i wonder why
What?! What?!
I was in danger?!
Danger, you say?
I suppose a mature woman like me
might strike you right in the heart.
Is that a joke? Who are you?
Who am I?
You don't recognize me?
I suppose I did waste away a
bit after that last battle.
But it's me, Shinobu.
What?!
Whatever happened to you?
I love it!
You're so lovely, it shocked
me right down to my bones.
Although, I suppose bones are all I got.
Bro, big bro!
Guess what?
Shinobu's going to teach
me to be a real Kunoichi.
I'll get real strong, so next time I see
you, you've got to let me join your crew.
Heck yeah, we could use a ninja.
So train hard.
You bet I will.
I'm going to be a bewitching
Kunoichi in no time, bro.
Ning, ning.
Otama, you are so precious.
Oh, I'm going to miss you most of all.
Now there's a shocker.
Pluton is in the land of Wano?
First Poseidon, and now this.
I know a certain someone who's going
to be very interested in this news.
Shogun!
I've been looking for you.
The plans are complete.
Reconstruction can begin shortly.
That's good.
I've included cost estimates
for each region as well. I see.
Excellent work.
Shogun, sir!
We have proposals to repurpose
the weapons factories.
They're just waiting for your approval.
Right. Let's go.
Excuse me.
Can you give me your opinion on the
reservoir when you have the time?
We should speak with
all the daimyo as well.
Let's schedule a meeting
in the near future.
Of course.
Hello, Shogun!
Hey, Zoro!
I'd like to learn a few sword techniques.
Do you think you could teach me? Hello?
Luffy! Zoro!
Onami!
Usopp!
Sanchi?
Chopper him on? Robin? Franky? Bonkichi?
Are you there, Jinbei?
Yamato?
Where did everyone go? Hello?
Hiyori, have you seen Luffy and his crew?
They said their farewells.
They're leaving the land of Wano now.
Sad, huh?
Said their farewells?
They didn't say a word to me.
There you are, Lord Momonosuke! Yes?
What's going on?
Is this about Luffy?
I just found out that he's departing!
You too?
This is so cruel!
I asked all the retainers, and the Straw
Hat spoke to every one of them but me!
Why would they exclude us when
we've known them the longest?
We're leaving today you don't get
to huh what does that mean don't
make it weird all right We can't
all sail off at the same time
our alliance is over remember
we're enemies now We're leaving
today because that's what we decided
on so did we the hell Trafalgar
This is my day. Pick
another. Yeah, no thanks.
You can change your own damn schedule.
Well, I'm not changing mine.
This is nothing but a waste of time.
Fine. How's this?
We'll go in different directions.
The log poe's locked onto
three different islands.
One is northeast, one's
east, and one's southeast.
Take your pick.
The metal hoist.
All right.
It's your problem now.
Heading northeast gets you
the farthest ahead, you know.
If you had half a brain cell
between you two, you'd get that.
The middle one?
Dumbasses.
I don't care what you do,
because I'm heading off now.
Have fun bickering.
All right, Straw Hat, let's draw for it.
When it goes east, lose it goes southeast.
I picked this one.
Ha!
I got east.
I messed up the draw!
I'm sorry, you guys!
Just help us load the sunny!
It's gonna be dangerous wherever we go!
So who cares?
I'm an emperor of the sea!
How could I lose it then? Huh?
Now you're pissing me off!
Still, there's one emperor
even lamer than you!
Can you believe this?
Buggy the Genius Jester.
What the heck?
Crocodile and Hawkeye are there too.
Huh?
They're making you look
like they work for Buggy.
What?
There's no way that's right.
Hawkeye wouldn't work for that clown.
If he really has those two under
his control, then I get it.
That alone would make
him emperor material.
Bucky's just a dumbass.
How'd he pull this off?
I couldn't tell you, but the new company
he's running is called Cross Guild,
and they've started putting bounties
on the heads of famous marines.
The Navy was always a hunter before,
but now anyone in the world can come
after them just like us pirates.
It seems that while we were
on our little getaway in Wind,
the entire world turned on its head.
Anyway, you know where
you're going, right?
Good thing we're headed in different
directions, because we're enemies from now on.
This is a parting gift?
What the hell is it?
It's a copy of a road poneglyph.
Poneglyph, you guys have
the right to this as well.
Cheating would take the fun out of it.
So Kaido did have one of them.
It's just like the thing we swiped
from one of Big Mom's generals.
We're in the endgame, kid.
We gotta get serious about this.
You know what we gotta do if we
wanna fight for the One Piece.
Find the man with the burn scar, right?
That's step one.
We don't have any leads, though. Huh?
Huh?
What burn scar?
Where'd you hear that?
You don't know?
Looks like I get a head start, huh?
Come on, just tell me!
Yamato!
Are you here?
You're not hiding from me, are you?
Yamato!
Hey, Momonosuke!
I'm up here!
Where is here?
On top of the roof, it would seem.
All right.
I've made up my mind.
Luffy, this is it. I'm ready.
Finally!
I'm going to live like Kozuki Oden!